https://www.healingherbs.co.uk/bach-essences/seven-helpers/

Skip to contentSeven HelpersThe Seven Helpers are the support essences and are selected for long-term emotional states. Dr Bach found these chronic conditions often obscure a person’s true nature as it is expressed within the Twelve Healers group.
Buy Online
Making
Choosing
Seven Helpers GorseHopelessness
HeatherTalkative
OakPersevering
OliveExhaustion
Rock WaterStrict idealist
VineDomineering
Wild OatLack of direction Making Healingherbs flower essencesHealingherbs are specialist Bach flower essence makers.  Our flower essences are made according to the original directions of Edward Bach with exceptional focus on creating the best quality essences.  Every essence is made by Julian Barnard personally using pure spring water and French organic brandy.
More info Selecting & using Bach flower essencesGuidance on how to choose, prepare and use Bach flower essences in your daily life.
More info
HomeBach EssencesBach EssencesTwelve HealersSeven HelpersSecond NineteenSeven Emotional Groups5 Flower®5 Flower® Drops, Spray & Granules5 Flower® Natural Cream5 Flower® Propolis Cream5 Flower® Propolis SoapNight Spray and GranulesExam Spray and GranulesChoosing and UsingChoosing and UsingHow to useEssence SelectorQuestions & AnswersOnline ShopAbout UsAbout UsMaking Our EssencesDr Edward BachPublicationsStudy CourseBach Educational ResourceCharitable TrustContact UsDelivery PolicyBlogCheckout
Login
We use cookies to enhance your experience. By continuing to visit this site you agree to our use of cookies. Learn more. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy Overview: This website makes use of cookies to enhance browsing experience and provide additional functionality. None of this data can or will be used to identify or contact you.
This website makes use of third party cookies, see the details in the privacy policy.
This website makes use of tracking cookies, see the details in the privacy policy.
To learn more about how this website uses cookies or localStorage, please read our PRIVACY POLICY.
By clicking Allow cookies you give your permission to this website to store small bits of data on your device.
To learn more about cookies and localStorage, visit Information Commissioner's Office.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website. Delivery PolicyUK Delivery – 10% of basket value or £4.25, whichever is the higher value (e.g Basket total = £20.00 – postage is £4.25. Basket total = £100.00 – postage is £10.00)Europe Standard [ Not trackable ] – 25% of basket value or £5.00, whichever is the higher valueEurope Signed For [ Trackable Online ] – 25% of basket or £5.00, whichever is higher value, plus £5.30Rest Of World* [ Not trackable ] – 35% of basket value or £6.00 whichever is higherRest Of World Tracked* [ Trackable Online ] – 35% of basket or £6.00, whichever is higher value, plus £5.30Note: trackable / traceable means you are able to find out where your package is in the delivery processTo cancel or modify your order please email: sales@healingherbs.co.uk for immediate responseApproximate delivery schedule by countryDelivery charges will be applied at checkout once your delivery details have been entered.We do not deliver items to the US or Mexico – we recommend you purchase directly from our distributors in the US or Mexico. ×
Email your selectionEmail your essence selection to yourself or a friend. This can help remind you of your personal essence selection.   ×
How to use the Essence SelectorThe HealingHerbs Essence Selector is a tool to help you make your own personal essence combination.You can use either the 12-7-19 Method or the 7 Emotional Groups.Your personal essence selectionYou can use the Quick View to see the emotional traits each essence is best suited for.You may then obtain your chosen essences in either 10ml or 30ml by clicking the Add to Basket button. Upon successful checkout, your order will be recorded in your account – this is useful so that you don’t need to remember your selections when you next order! ×
SHARE YOUR BASKET Login Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
Log in Lost your password?Register Email address * A password will be sent to your email address.Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
Register
